[["The benchmark includes mainly investment-grade corporate bonds denominated in USD, EUR and GBP, with exposure to bonds denominated in any given currency limited to below 50%\n", {"entities": [[164, 173, "PERCENT"], [4, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"], [78, 81, "GPE"], [83, 86, "GPE"], [91, 94, "ORG"], [57, 62, "ASSET"]]}],
["Hedge to USD to mitigate volatility and provide returns that can then be hedged\n", {"entities": [[56, 60, "NEW_ENTITY"], [9, 12, "ORG"], [9, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Over 40 sector specialists cover the global credit universe across investment grade, cross-over and high yield names\n", {"entities": [[51, 59, "NEW_ENTITY"], [15, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 7, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["By investing the crossover space, we are able to target the yield potential of high yield bonds while maintaining an overall lower risk profile\n", {"entities": [[27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"], [34, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We use a regional approach, breaking down the investment universe into US, Europe and emerging markets for enhanced diversification\n", {"entities": [[18, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"], [75, 81, "LOC"], [71, 73, "GPE"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We use our local credit management and credit research teams to determine issuer, regional, sector and credit allocations.\n", {"entities": [[55, 60, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Certain investors are limited to investment grade credit and others to high yield.As a bond changes categories, managers are forced to sell, creating opportunities for managers that can hold transitioning bonds\n", {"entities": [[8, 17, "NEW_ENTITY"], [50, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Proprietary fundamental and valuation research tools are critical to our investment decisions and our risk calibration techniques\n", {"entities": [[47, 52, "NEW_ENTITY"], [84, 93, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Lead portfolio managers leverage the insights of local credit analysts and portfolio managers and actively allocate across regions (US, Europe and emerging markets)\n", {"entities": [[37, 45, "NEW_ENTITY"], [136, 142, "LOC"], [132, 134, "GPE"], [15, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The lead fund manager allocates assets across US, Euro and emerging markets sleeves to capture different yield, quality, duration and volatility characteristics\n", {"entities": [[32, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [46, 48, "GPE"], [14, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["We believe bonds in the crossover space are inefficient as technical factors and market overreactions often lead to mispricing\n", {"entities": [[34, 39, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The strategy focuses on high yield opportunities in the US, Europe and emerging markets.We also manage a Global Short Duration High Yield Bond strategy, which aims to provide attractive returns with lower duration and volatility.\n", {"entities": [[105, 126, "EVENT"], [35, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 66, "LOC"], [56, 58, "GPE"]]}],
["The value of investments may go down as well as up and you may not get back the amount originally invested.Fixed income is subject to credit and interest rate risk.Investments in high yield securities (commonly referred to as “junk bonds”) are often considered speculative investments and have significantly higher credit risk than investment grade securities.The prices of high yield securities, which may be less liquid than higher rated securities, may be more volatile and more vulnerable to adverse market, economic or political conditions.Investments in emerging markets are by their nature higher risk and potentially more volatile than those inherent in some established markets.Derivatives can be illiquid, may disproportionately increase losses and may have a potentially large negative impact on performance.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our global credit strategies seek attractive risk-adjusted returns with an emphasis on income and yield.\n", {"entities": [[59, 66, "NEW_ENTITY"], [18, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our global credit strategies invest in securities with stable or improving fundamentals, focusing on mispriced risks.\n", {"entities": [[39, 49, "NEW_ENTITY"], [18, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The geographic reach and local insights of our global credit platform support the investment team in sifting through the broad opportunity set\n", {"entities": [[15, 20, "NEW_ENTITY"], [61, 69, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Diversification is a key consideration in portfolio construction\n", {"entities": [[52, 64, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our customised benchmark seeks to provide more attractive risk-adjusted returns over the medium-term than the traditional benchmark\n", {"entities": [[15, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"], [72, 79, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The strategy invests in high yield corporate bonds with the ability to invest in investment grade or lower rated high yield bonds opportunistically\n", {"entities": [[45, 50, "ASSET"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We have developed a customised benchmark, the Bloomberg Barclays High Income Bond Composite Index, to expand the investment grade opportunity set globally to include higher rated high yield credit\n", {"entities": [[31, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Many of our global credit strategies use alternatively-weighted, customised benchmarks targeting more attractive risk-adjusted returns\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [26, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our credit analysts focus on specific credits rather than ratings, allowing for continuity in coverage to provide the investment team with in-depth insights on the credit\n", {"entities": [[38, 45, "NEW_ENTITY"], [11, 19, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Diversification is a key consideration in our benchmark and portfolio construction\n", {"entities": [[70, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We have created a customised benchmark - the Bloomberg Barclays Global Aggregates Corporate Alternatively Weighted Scheme Index Hedged USD\n", {"entities": [[29, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Proprietary fundamental, quantitative and decision support tools facilitate insight development, team debate, effectiveness and productivity\n", {"entities": [[59, 64, "NEW_ENTITY"], [84, 95, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Tools for pricing, combining and calibrating risk are integrated in the portfolio construction process\n", {"entities": [[0, 5, "NEW_ENTITY"], [10, 17, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["A well-established fundamental relationship exists between company profitability and valuation.\n", {"entities": [[67, 80, "NEW_ENTITY"], [31, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Proprietary fundamental research tools incorporate Environment, Social, and Governance (ESG) analysis: confirming the sustainability of profitability and validating the investment opportunity\n", {"entities": [[76, 86, "ORG"], [33, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [51, 62, "NEW_ENTITY"], [88, 91, "ORG"], [64, 70, "ORG"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Over time, markets tend to reflect relative intrinsic value, rewarding patient investors with strict valuation disciplines and longer-term investment horizons\n", {"entities": [[11, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We aim to deliver high conviction and high active share portfolios that are differentiated by design.\n", {"entities": [[23, 33, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We leverage the intellectual capital of a global network of investment professionals and resources to deliver consistently strong long-term results\n", {"entities": [[29, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["Global, regional and country-specific strategies have been designed to meet a broad spectrum of investment goals\n", {"entities": [[84, 92, "NEW_ENTITY"], [38, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Excess market volatility suggests that risks and fundamentals may be misunderstood—creating potential opportunities that should be confirmed by fundamental research\n", {"entities": [[102, 115, "NEW_ENTITY"], [14, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our active equity strategies are tailored to meet specific client investment objectives with a disciplined and differentiated investment approach.\n", {"entities": [[77, 87, "NEW_ENTITY"], [18, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Investment universe is ranked based on profitability and valuation to highlight relative value opportunities\n", {"entities": [[39, 52, "NEW_ENTITY"], [11, 19, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["In the short-term, markets can be inefficient due to varying perspectives, risk aversion and behavioural biases\n", {"entities": [[19, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 17, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.Where overseas investments are held the rate of currency exchange may also cause the value of such investments to fluctuate.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["The HSBC Global Equity Income fund invests globally in stocks listed in both developed and emerging markets.The investment team takes advantage of the insights and perspectives of our investment specialists on the ground in different markets across the globe.\n", {"entities": [[30, 34, "PRODUCT"], [55, 61, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 8, "ORG"]]}],
["HSBC has a long history of over 30 years’ experience in managing equity solutions, with over 200 investment professionals and USD74.2 billion under management as at December 2017.The global equity team compromises 13 investment professionals.\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [93, 96, "CARDINAL"], [165, 173, "DATE"], [32, 41, "DATE"], [0, 4, "ORG"], [214, 216, "CARDINAL"], [16, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of an investment in the portfolios and any income from them can go down as well as up and as with any investment you may not receive back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Listed property securities are part of the equity market and are more volatile than direct (unlisted) property, which can mean that the price of Shares and the income from them can fluctuate, sometimes dramatically\n", {"entities": [[50, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Property values are affected by a number of factors, including general and local economic conditions, attractiveness and location of properties, increases in local competition, financial condition of tenants, quality of maintenance, limitations on and variations in rents, level of investor demand and changes in interest rates\n", {"entities": [[9, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"], [34, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We actively allocate between direct property funds and listed property equity funds.  Our investments are held indirectly, mainly through funds, rather than by owning buildings directly.This approach helps to access local markets quickly and easily, using specialist managers, as well as diversifying property-specific risk efficiently.\n", {"entities": [[45, 50, "PRODUCT"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Some of the underlying property funds will not price daily\n", {"entities": [[32, 37, "PRODUCT"], [0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [53, 58, "DATE"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["Since 2007, the HSBC Global Property Fund has provided investors with globally-diversified access to direct (unlisted) property and listed property via quoted real estate equities in a single fund.\n", {"entities": [[6, 10, "DATE"], [6, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"], [12, 41, "ORG"], [37, 41, "PRODUCT"]]}],
["There are three reasons behind our approach to blending listed and unlisted property.Combining funds that invest in direct property with and those that invest in property equities offers potentially lower volatility of returns than would be the case from investing in equity markets alone.It also helps to maintain higher liquidity than is possible when investing only in direct property.Finally, investing in both types of property provides the opportunity to enhance returns as their relative attractiveness varies over time.\n", {"entities": [[101, 105, "NEW_ENTITY"], [10, 15, "CARDINAL"], [35, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["There are certain additional costs and risks associated with the direct ownership of real estate.These include: risk of oversupply in local markets, risk of extended vacancies within properties, property taxes and operating expenses, risk of changes in planning laws, risks relating to legal title,costs relating to environmental problems and liability risk to third parties for damages resulting from environmental problems, and uninsured damages from floods, earthquakes and other natural disasters\n", {"entities": [[72, 81, "NEW_ENTITY"], [97, 102, "NEW_ENTITY"], [361, 366, "ORDINAL"]]}],
["20 countries, investing in over 640 buildings (direct property funds), and over 100 listed property securities that own 100s of buildings plus 50+ directly-held property equities\n", {"entities": [[32, 35, "CARDINAL"], [111, 115, "NEW_ENTITY"], [120, 124, "CARDINAL"], [75, 83, "CARDINAL"], [0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [36, 45, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["HSBC Global Property Fund offers exposure to*\n", {"entities": [[33, 41, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 25, "ORG"], [21, 25, "PRODUCT"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The fund is daily dealt and priced and has never suspended redemptions\n", {"entities": [[59, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 8, "PRODUCT"], [12, 17, "DATE"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of an investment in the portfolios and any income from them can go down as well as up and as with any investment you may not receive back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["What are some of the risks when investing?\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [9, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Commercial and residential property have different risk profiles and returns in one market do not necessarily follow the other.The risks involved in property investment are different from other types of investments such as equities and bonds, in that this type of investment tends to lag the economic cycle rather than lead it\n", {"entities": [[80, 83, "CARDINAL"], [56, 64, "NEW_ENTITY"], [27, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Your clients can choose from one of five globally diversified managed portfolios – each intended for a different risk profile.And since you don’t need to worry about managing portfolios or rebalancing asset allocation, you can focus your attention on your clients and attracting new business.We know you value your freedom – to offer your clients the best service, grow your business and take advantage of opportunities when they arise.The HSBC Global Managed Portfolio Service is designed specifically to help you to do just that.\n", {"entities": [[29, 32, "CARDINAL"], [436, 477, "ORG"], [5, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 40, "CARDINAL"], [29, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["Consider how understanding financial risk can help you reach your investment goals, from the impact of inflation on your cash savings to spreading your investments across different markets.\n", {"entities": [[37, 41, "RISK"], [51, 54, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Local expertise makes it easier for us to discover potential opportunities.It also means there are fewer constraints in bringing you and your clients quality ideas.Plus, our considerable resources give us the buying power to deliver these opportunities more cost-effectively.\n", {"entities": [[61, 74, "NEW_ENTITY"], [6, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Find out why retail investors get the same level of investment expertise as corporate clients.\n", {"entities": [[20, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [43, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of an investment in the portfolios and any income from them can go down as well as up and as with any investment you may not receive back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["See how the Global Managed Portfolio Service offers a transparent and highly cost-efficient diversified access to global markets.\n", {"entities": [[104, 110, "NEW_ENTITY"], [37, 44, "PRODUCT"], [8, 44, "ORG"]]}],
["Offering ‘global reach’ is one thing, but what does that really mean for financial advisers in the UK?When you work with HSBC, it means investment experts based locally – in key locations throughout the world – so nothing gets lost in translation.\n", {"entities": [[0, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"], [17, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [121, 125, "ORG"], [27, 30, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["Investments in emerging markets are by their nature higher risk and potentially more volatile than those inherent in some established markets\n", {"entities": [[0, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"], [24, 31, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["A strict risk management framework is used to validate our investment ideas; we use robust stress-testing and scenario analysis tools to continuously calibrate and optimize portfolio exposures\n", {"entities": [[25, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"], [70, 75, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Emerging markets are part of our corporate DNA and we have one of the longest track records in the industry.\n", {"entities": [[9, 16, "NEW_ENTITY"], [43, 46, "NEW_ENTITY"], [59, 62, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We assess economic and fundamental EMD drivers with relative value analytics, market dynamics and technical factors to model the initial portfolio positions\n", {"entities": [[39, 46, "NEW_ENTITY"], [35, 38, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["Against the backdrop of key macroeconomic and market dynamics, we focus on EM country and issuer fundamentals and relative valuations to determine our security selection and initial portfolio positioning\n", {"entities": [[63, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [12, 20, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our Emerging Markets Debt (EMD) team exercises a robust, consistent and collaborative investment process with the aim of achieving superior risk-adjusted returns over the longer-term.\n", {"entities": [[32, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [97, 104, "NEW_ENTITY"], [27, 30, "ORG"]]}],
["Investments in high yield securities (commonly referred to as “junk bonds”) are often considered speculative investments and have significantly higher credit risk than investment grade securities.The prices of high yield securities, which may be less liquid than higher rated securities, may be more volatile and more vulnerable to adverse market, economic or political conditions\n", {"entities": [[0, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"], [26, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["EMD has evolved into a complex asset class and requires specialized resources to identify opportunities and risks that may be mispriced or misunderstood.We believe EMD markets reflect fundamental values over the longer-term, but can be highly inefficient over the shorter-term.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [164, 167, "ORG"], [37, 42, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of investments may go down as well as up and you may not get back the amount originally invested\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Portfolio management decisions incorporate the expertise and analysis of a large, dedicated team of EMD specialists, credit analysts and economists.The process is collaborative and dynamic: specialists are each responsible and accountable for numerous investment inputs and decisions.\n", {"entities": [[100, 103, "ORG"], [21, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["EMD capabilities range from US dollar-denominated sovereign, quasi-sovereign and corporate bonds to local currency-denominated debt and local FX.We offer both benchmarked and total return strategies in this space\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [4, 16, "NEW_ENTITY"], [91, 96, "ASSET"], [28, 30, "GPE"]]}],
["Our model portfolios then undergo rigorous stress-testing and scenario analysis to fine-tune initial position sizing/scaling as well as to recalibrate and optimize positions over time\n", {"entities": [[50, 57, "NEW_ENTITY"], [10, 20, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Fixed income is subject to credit and interest rate risk.Credit risk refers to the ability of an issuer to make timely payments of interest and principal.Interest rate risk refers to fluctuations in the value of a fixed income security that result from changes in the general level of interest rates.In a declining interest rate environment, a portfolio may generate less income.In a rising interest-rate environment, bond prices fall\n", {"entities": [[6, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [52, 56, "RISK"]]}],
["Our global platform connects and supports an on-the-ground network of analysts and investment professionals across the world, leveraging their extensive local knowledge and insights\n", {"entities": [[52, 58, "NEW_ENTITY"], [11, 19, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We capture macroeconomic views, catalysts and investment themes together with detailed EM country and currency fundamentals and relative valuation metrics to guide our investment approach.Reiterative risk management is a critical to our process.We continuously assess the numerous external factors impacting EMD to fine-tune our positioning and to ensure we have optimized the portfolio for acceptable risk/return trade-offs.\n", {"entities": [[308, 311, "ORG"], [25, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["A broad investment universe: the fund invests globally, on both investment grade and high yield bonds, leveraging our expertise in each of these market segments\n", {"entities": [[75, 80, "NEW_ENTITY"], [33, 37, "PRODUCT"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The fund is based on a disciplined, active management approach, backed by proprietary research.Our bespoke benchmark has been constructed to offer a broad range of opportunities with a potentially attractive combination of return and risk.\n", {"entities": [[54, 62, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 8, "PRODUCT"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["With over 170 professional investors – including +40 credit analysts globally – and 192USD billion under management as at December 2017, we are able to connect UK investors with fixed income opportunities, in most geographies and across all market segments\n", {"entities": [[27, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [160, 162, "GPE"], [84, 98, "CARDINAL"], [122, 135, "DATE"], [10, 13, "CARDINAL"], [137, 139, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["global credit platform leverages our geographic reach for direct access to experienced global teams of fund managers and credit research analysts.Identifying, pricing and combining risks is at the core of our investment approach.\n", {"entities": [[14, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [48, 53, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The lead fund manager allocates assets across the US, Europe, Emerging markets and ABS sleeves.Individual sleeves are managed by HSBC’s expert portfolio managers based locally across the globe who position the portfolio across countries, issuers and sectors.\n", {"entities": [[50, 52, "GPE"], [32, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [14, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [54, 60, "LOC"], [129, 133, "ORG"]]}],
["The value of an investment in the portfolios and any income from them can go down as well as up and as with any investment you may not receive back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The HSBC GIF Global High Income Bond Fund focuses on income generation, and is aimed at those investors who seek to overcome today’s low-interest environment.The fund aims to deliver a combination of sustainable income and capital appreciation by seeking the best investment opportunities across fixed income global markets.\n", {"entities": [[37, 41, "PRODUCT"], [60, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"], [125, 130, "DATE"], [4, 8, "ORG"]]}],
["The investment characteristics of securitised credit differ from traditional debt securities.The major difference is that the principal is often paid in stages and may be fully repaid at any time because of the terms of the underlying loans.This variability in timing of cash flows makes estimates of future asset yield and weighted average life uncertain.There may also be specific risks involved when investing in securitised credit, including pre-payment risk, subordinated risk, capital value risk, economic risk, re-financing risk and liquidity risk.\n", {"entities": [[15, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [46, 52, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["An established and experienced team of 15 dedicated specialists, forms one of the largest structured credit teams in the industry\n", {"entities": [[52, 63, "NEW_ENTITY"], [31, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 41, "CARDINAL"], [71, 74, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["What are some of the risks?\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [9, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["We invest in all securitised credit sectors, across all rating categories and do so “globally” from one platform in London.Our global scale and investment tools support:\n", {"entities": [[116, 122, "GPE"], [100, 103, "CARDINAL"], [36, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.The value of the underlying assets is strongly affected by interest rate fluctuations and by changes in the credit ratings of the underlying issuer of the assets.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["A seamless capacity to invest where we are finding best opportunities\n", {"entities": [[56, 69, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our global reach differentiates us from many competitors that focus purely on US and/or European ABS\n", {"entities": [[11, 16, "NEW_ENTITY"], [88, 96, "NORP"], [78, 80, "GPE"], [32, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Securitised credit offers substantial opportunities reflecting misunderstood or mispriced risk.\n", {"entities": [[0, 11, "ORG"], [12, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [38, 51, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Significant market access to a wide range of structured credit opportunities which is not easily replicated in the structured credit space\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 41, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Access to significant trading flows where we can use our relationships and size to negotiate attractive prices for clients\n", {"entities": [[30, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"], [42, 44, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Securitised credit can be a beneficial addition to a portfolio for four main reasons:\n", {"entities": [[0, 11, "ORG"], [53, 62, "NEW_ENTITY"], [67, 71, "CARDINAL"], [12, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We believe it supports the delivery of the Paris Climate Agreement and the UN Sustainable Development Goals\n", {"entities": [[27, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"], [71, 107, "LAW"], [39, 66, "LAW"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["Active stewardship is an essential part of our approach.We use our influence as a global asset manager with a long-term investment approach to engage directly with the companies we own on behalf of our clients, to encourage best practices.\n", {"entities": [[7, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 55, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["What does sustainable investment means to us?\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [22, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our aim is to deliver against 3 priorities:\n", {"entities": [[30, 31, "CARDINAL"], [4, 7, "NEW_ENTITY"], [32, 42, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We believe it considers the environment and society\n", {"entities": [[28, 39, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of an investment in the portfolios and any income from them can go down as well as up and as with any investment you may not receive back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The state of our planet, wellbeing of society and behaviour of corporations are all related issues with significant consequences and we believe that company performance can be positively influenced by good sustainability practices.\n", {"entities": [[17, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We believe it builds on the foundations of our commitment to the Principles of Responsible Investment and active stewardship\n", {"entities": [[61, 101, "LAW"], [28, 39, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The key types of risk associated with the Global Sustainable Multi-Asset Portfolios are as follows (please refer to the KIID for the full list):\n", {"entities": [[17, 21, "RISK"], [8, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"], [120, 124, "ORG"]]}],
["As the global economy evolves to address sustainability issues, it creates opportunities and risks for companies.Some will stand to gain from the adaptation of new standards and technologies.Companies that most effectively manage opportunities and risks related to sustainability should logically find long-term success.\n", {"entities": [[56, 62, "NEW_ENTITY"], [14, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["With one of the largest and most experienced networks of credit research talent in the asset management industry, we have the resources to achieve competitive risk-adjusted returns.\n", {"entities": [[5, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"], [114, 116, "NEW_ENTITY"], [5, 8, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["A strong team-based approach incorporates wider perspectives for better, more resilient long-term outcomes.\n", {"entities": [[48, 60, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Cost efficient beta management to be used as building block or to adjust allocations\n", {"entities": [[54, 59, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beta positioning that reflects economic and credit cycle anticipations\n", {"entities": [[17, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [57, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.The value of the underlying assets is strongly affected by interest rate fluctuations and by changes in the credit ratings of the underlying issuer of the assets.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["AWS avoid the well-known shortcomings of market cap-weighted indices: concentration and drifts in credit quality and allocation\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [25, 37, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Some segments present ineffective risk / return profiles and should be avoided\n", {"entities": [[48, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"], [5, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our fixed income strategies are designed to deliver the benefits of a global platform with local investment team autonomy.This approach enables us to provide a targeted range of global, regional and single country investment strategies.\n", {"entities": [[56, 64, "NEW_ENTITY"], [17, 27, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our investment culture empowers flexible and timely portfolio management decisions.The global platform ensures robust, transparent and consistent processes.\n", {"entities": [[73, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [15, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our global fixed income platform is supported by 200 portfolio management professionals and around 50 seasoned credit analysts specialised by geography and by sector.\n", {"entities": [[74, 87, "NEW_ENTITY"], [92, 101, "CARDINAL"], [24, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"], [49, 52, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our international fixed income specialists, supported by our global research platform, focus on delivering strong risk-adjusted returns.We offer a comprehensive range of strategies to meet client objectives.\n", {"entities": [[31, 42, "NEW_ENTITY"], [77, 85, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["On August 23, President Donald Trump said the US would lift tariffs on USD250 billion of Chinese goods to 30% from 25% with effect from October 1, and increase the levy on the remaining USD300 billion of imports from China, which include clothing and footwear, to 15% from 10%.The second tariff rate increase will take effect in two stages, on September 1 and December 1\n", {"entities": [[31, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [344, 370, "DATE"], [329, 332, "CARDINAL"], [24, 36, "PERSON"], [115, 118, "PERCENT"], [136, 145, "DATE"], [46, 48, "GPE"], [89, 96, "NORP"], [264, 267, "PERCENT"], [186, 200, "CARDINAL"], [217, 222, "GPE"], [273, 287, "CARDINAL"], [71, 85, "FAC"], [3, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [106, 109, "PERCENT"], [3, 12, "DATE"]]}],
["On a brighter note, the US President on 26 th of August predicted a trade deal with China after positive gestures by Beijing, helping calm markets that have been roiled by the new rounds of tariffs\n", {"entities": [[27, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [84, 89, "GPE"], [40, 55, "DATE"], [24, 26, "GPE"], [117, 124, "GPE"], [14, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["On a month to date basis, only two of the 11 sectors included in MSCI China in August advanced, with companies in the healthcare and consumer staple rising 3.7% and 1.9%, respectively.Conversely, energy and communication services retreated 11.2% and 8.3%, reflecting concerns over an economic slowdown and a selloff in telecom companies\n", {"entities": [[156, 160, "PERCENT"], [79, 85, "DATE"], [250, 254, "PERCENT"], [65, 75, "GPE"], [165, 169, "PERCENT"], [31, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 10, "DATE"], [26, 34, "CARDINAL"], [240, 245, "PERCENT"], [5, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"], [42, 44, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["Going forward, we favour government and policy bank papers on the back of expectations that interest rates would be lower for longer, while remaining constructive on a few high beta names that should benefit from further easing measures\n", {"entities": [[15, 17, "NEW_ENTITY"], [52, 58, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The amount of bonds globally carrying negative yields increased to an all time high of more than USD16 trillion in August, as fears over recession have pushed investors to buy more haven assets.Germany, for instance, sold 30 year bonds with a negative yield for the first time, a milestone for the fixed income market where the entire yield curve yields less than zero\n", {"entities": [[354, 368, "CARDINAL"], [222, 229, "DATE"], [194, 201, "GPE"], [115, 121, "DATE"], [4, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"], [14, 19, "ASSET"], [266, 271, "ORDINAL"]]}],
["US China trade tensions escalated in August as both sides raised the tariffs modestly and rhetoric considerably.On the 23 rd , the US ordered American companies to find alternatives to China and dialled up tariffs after China applied duties on USD75 billion of US imports.To be sure, escalated tariffs could point to more depreciation pressure on the renminbi , but authorities may believe that a prolonged depreciation path does not seem to be in the best interests of the economy either\n", {"entities": [[220, 225, "GPE"], [261, 263, "GPE"], [119, 121, "CARDINAL"], [0, 2, "GPE"], [15, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 8, "GPE"], [37, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [185, 190, "GPE"], [37, 43, "DATE"], [142, 150, "NORP"], [131, 133, "GPE"]]}],
["Effective from October 8, the interest rate on individual mortgages for first time homebuyers cannot be lower than the five year LPR, and the rate on loans for second time homebuyers cannot be lower than the LPR plus 60bps, according to the PBoC. Payments on outstanding mortgage loans remain unchanged\n", {"entities": [[39, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [129, 132, "ORG"], [160, 166, "ORDINAL"], [208, 211, "ORG"], [115, 128, "DATE"], [15, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [237, 255, "ORG"], [15, 24, "DATE"], [72, 77, "ORDINAL"]]}],
["Average new home prices in the country’s70 major cities advanced 0.6% in July from the previous month, making it the 51st consecutive monthly gain, according to the National Bureau of Statistics.The data show nationwide property prices rose 9.7% on a year on year basis in July, the slowest growth this year, moderating from a 10.3% gain in June.\n", {"entities": [[327, 332, "PERCENT"], [17, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [49, 55, "NEW_ENTITY"], [134, 141, "DATE"], [73, 77, "DATE"], [298, 307, "DATE"], [341, 345, "DATE"], [65, 69, "PERCENT"], [241, 245, "PERCENT"], [273, 277, "DATE"], [249, 255, "DATE"], [117, 121, "ORDINAL"], [161, 194, "ORG"], [259, 263, "DATE"], [83, 101, "DATE"]]}],
["The July data on new loans came in lower than expectations, while the growth in money supply and total social financing (TSF) also moderated.Chinese banks extended RMB1.06 trillion in net loans in July, down from RMB1.66 trillion in June and falling short of expectations.The broadest measure of money supply, M2, expanded 8.1% year on year in July, down from an 8.5% increase in June.Growth in TSF softened to 10.7% from 10.9% over the same period\n", {"entities": [[422, 427, "PERCENT"], [344, 348, "DATE"], [4, 8, "DATE"], [197, 201, "DATE"], [233, 237, "DATE"], [310, 312, "FAC"], [336, 340, "DATE"], [380, 384, "DATE"], [164, 180, "CARDINAL"], [433, 448, "DATE"], [121, 124, "ORG"], [213, 229, "MONEY"], [323, 327, "PERCENT"], [141, 148, "NORP"], [363, 367, "PERCENT"], [411, 416, "PERCENT"], [21, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"], [9, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"], [395, 398, "ORG"], [328, 332, "DATE"]]}],
["In China, the yield curve of government bonds remained largely unchanged in August, but the yield on benchmark 10 year bonds dipped below the 3% mark for the first time on August 15.The yield was hovering around 3% by late August\n", {"entities": [[158, 163, "ORDINAL"], [111, 118, "DATE"], [3, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 8, "GPE"], [20, 25, "NEW_ENTITY"], [76, 82, "DATE"], [172, 178, "DATE"], [218, 229, "DATE"], [205, 214, "PERCENT"], [142, 144, "PERCENT"]]}],
["Any forecast, projection or target contained in this presentation is for information purposes only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC Global Asset Management accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecasts, projections or targets.\n", {"entities": [[53, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [132, 160, "ORG"]]}],
["To be announced monthly, the LPR pricing will take the arithmetic average of what a group of designated banks charge their clients, expressed as the spread over the one year medium term lending facility ( MLF).The MLF is a rate at which commercial banks borrow from the central bank, and is viewed as a better indication of the latest credit conditions.\n", {"entities": [[33, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"], [29, 32, "ORG"], [161, 173, "DATE"], [16, 23, "DATE"], [66, 73, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We use cookies\n", {"entities": [[7, 14, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This is blank file acting as a renderer for ttm cloudservice\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [44, 61, "ORG"], [31, 39, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["However, overall sales of residential property projects remain sluggish, prompting developers to cut prices.In the first seven months, growth in residential projects contracted 0.4%, compared with a 1 % decline in the first six months\n", {"entities": [[17, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 55, "NEW_ENTITY"], [199, 202, "PERCENT"], [177, 181, "PERCENT"], [111, 133, "DATE"], [214, 234, "DATE"]]}],
["Any forecast, projection or target contained in this presentation is for information purposes only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecasts, projections or targets.\n", {"entities": [[53, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [132, 136, "ORG"]]}],
["There are, however, signs that policymakers want to keep the runaway prices under control, with new tightening measures to rein in credit for both developers and homebuyers.\n", {"entities": [[69, 75, "NEW_ENTITY"], [31, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["According to PBoC Governor Yi Gang, the government wants to maintain stability in the property market and will ensure that the cost of household mortgages will remain largely stable a bid to push down the cost of borrowing without further inflating property prices\n", {"entities": [[27, 34, "PERSON"], [30, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"], [40, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Given the minimal difference between the new and old lending rates, we think the impact on the mortgage market will take some time to be felt.In the longer term, the premium over the LPR should better reflect each bank’s lending appetite and its own assessment of credit risks, helping develop a market driven pricing mechanism\n", {"entities": [[183, 186, "ORG"], [18, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [68, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["For illustrative purposes only and does not constitute any investment recommendation in the above mentioned asset classes, in dic es or currencies.The views and opinions expressed herein are subject to change at any time.\n", {"entities": [[151, 156, "NEW_ENTITY"], [126, 132, "GPE"], [17, 25, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["On August 20, the PBoC set the one year LPR at 4.25% and the five year rate at 4.85 %.Those rates will be used as the benchmark for long term loans such as household mortgages.The new one year LPR was down 6bps from 4.31% previously.It was also 10bps lower than the previous benchmark one year lending rate of 4.35\n", {"entities": [[206, 210, "CARDINAL"], [47, 52, "PERCENT"], [310, 314, "CARDINAL"], [193, 196, "ORG"], [216, 221, "PERCENT"], [18, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [245, 250, "CARDINAL"], [61, 70, "DATE"], [184, 192, "DATE"], [27, 39, "DATE"], [3, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [40, 43, "ORG"], [285, 293, "DATE"], [79, 85, "PERCENT"], [3, 12, "DATE"]]}],
["China’s property prices have continued to rise so far this year despite a prolonged trade conflict with the US.\n", {"entities": [[17, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 5, "GPE"], [90, 98, "NEW_ENTITY"], [108, 110, "GPE"], [54, 63, "DATE"]]}],
["Any forecast, projection or target contained in this presentation is for information purposes only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC Global Asset Management accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecasts, projections or targets\n", {"entities": [[53, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [132, 160, "ORG"]]}],
["Our website doesn't support your browserso please upgrade\n", {"entities": [[33, 42, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Capital at risk.Eligibility criteria and terms apply\n", {"entities": [[11, 15, "RISK"], [28, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Onshore and offshore renminbi bonds advanced 0.83% and 0.34% in August (up to the 26th), respectively, joining the big global rally in sovereign bonds.Currently, investors still expect further loosening measures by Beijing, after the latest set of weak economic data strengthened the case for further monetary easing\n", {"entities": [[55, 60, "PERCENT"], [82, 86, "ORDINAL"], [64, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"], [215, 222, "GPE"], [64, 70, "DATE"], [45, 50, "PERCENT"], [30, 35, "ASSET"]]}],
["Fund flows into China’s A share market through the Stock Connect reversed in August, with net selling of USD640 million of shares, while net purchases of Hong Kong shares advanced for a sixth consecutive month, with net purchases of USD6.6 billion of shares.Meanwhile, MSCI’s schedule to raise the inclusion factor for A shares to 15% from 10% after the close of markets on August 27 is expected to draw USD4.5 billion of passive net inflows\n", {"entities": [[16, 21, "GPE"], [411, 418, "CARDINAL"], [184, 209, "DATE"], [0, 4, "PRODUCT"], [77, 83, "DATE"], [331, 334, "PERCENT"], [32, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [340, 343, "PERCENT"], [105, 119, "CARDINAL"], [374, 383, "DATE"], [154, 163, "GPE"], [269, 273, "ORG"], [47, 64, "ORG"]]}],
["This commentary provides a high level overview of the recent economic environment, and is for information purposes only.It is a marketing communication and does not constitute investment advice or a recommendation to any reader of this content to buy or sell investments nor should it be regarded as investment research.It has not been prepared in accordance with legal requirements designed to promote the independence of investment research and is not subject to any prohibition on dealing ahead of its dissemination.The performance figures displayed in the document relate to the past and past performance should not be seen as an indication of future returns.Any forecast, projection or target where provided is indicative only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC Global Asset Management accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecast, projection or target.\n", {"entities": [[38, 46, "NEW_ENTITY"], [765, 793, "ORG"], [5, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["In other key macro data, the growth in industrial output a broad measure of manufacturing production rose 4.8% in July, its weakest rate since February 2002.Retail sales expanded by 7.6% in July, their weakest rate since April\n", {"entities": [[29, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"], [190, 194, "DATE"], [106, 110, "PERCENT"], [19, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [221, 227, "DATE"], [143, 163, "DATE"], [114, 118, "DATE"], [182, 186, "PERCENT"]]}],
["Any forecast, projection or target contained in this presentation is for information purposes only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC Global Asset Management accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecasts, projections or targets.For illustrative purposes only.\n", {"entities": [[53, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [132, 160, "ORG"]]}],
["As for ordinary homebuyers, the introduction in August of a new benchmark interest rate by the People’s Bank of China will start to have a gradual impact on mortgage payments made each month.\n", {"entities": [[180, 190, "DATE"], [32, 44, "NEW_ENTITY"], [48, 54, "DATE"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"], [91, 117, "ORG"]]}],
["The US was responding to Beijing’s decision earlier to impose additional tariffs, ranging from 5% to 10%, on USD75 billion of US goods that include soybeans and frozen pork.Beijing’s retaliatory move was a response to the US decision earlier in August to impose a 10% tariff on USD300 billion worth of Chinese imports from September, before Washington said it would delay imposing duties on about half of those China made products until mid December\n", {"entities": [[278, 292, "MONEY"], [25, 32, "GPE"], [95, 104, "PERCENT"], [437, 450, "DATE"], [4, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"], [35, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [173, 180, "GPE"], [4, 6, "GPE"], [126, 128, "GPE"], [222, 224, "GPE"], [264, 267, "PERCENT"], [245, 251, "DATE"], [411, 416, "GPE"], [302, 309, "NORP"], [391, 401, "CARDINAL"], [323, 332, "DATE"], [341, 351, "GPE"]]}],
["Investment involves risks.Past performance is not indicative of future performance\n", {"entities": [[20, 25, "RISK"], [0, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Any forecast, projection or target contained in this presentation is for information purposes only and is not guaranteed in any way.HSBC Global Asset Management accepts no liability for any failure to meet such forecasts, projections or targets.For illustrative pu rposes only.\n", {"entities": [[53, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [262, 271, "PERSON"], [4, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [132, 160, "ORG"]]}],
["The National Development Reform Commission, the countrytop economic planner, in July tightened the grip on the issuance of offshore debt, curtailing developers’ appetite for new debt issuance.Specifically, developers can only issue debt to refinance outstanding foreign-currency liabilities in the next 12 months, a move intended to cool land market auctions in the country.\n", {"entities": [[80, 84, "NEW_ENTITY"], [80, 84, "DATE"], [0, 42, "ORG"], [294, 312, "DATE"], [32, 42, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["However, soaring prices have complicated efforts to spur growth as policy makers monitor downside risks\n", {"entities": [[17, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [41, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["In our view, the authorities want to contain credit risks in the property market without undermining broader efforts to spur a slowing economy.There have also been concerns that high property prices would be reducing consumer spending, which top officials hope would support growth\n", {"entities": [[7, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"], [17, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["MSCI China and the onshore benchmark CSI 300 Index retreated in the month of August, raising concerns that the latest round of trade escalation between the US and China poses a heightened threat to global growth.As of 26 th August, the former and latter fell 6% and 5.3% (USD terms) on a monthly basis, respectively\n", {"entities": [[266, 270, "PERCENT"], [259, 261, "PERCENT"], [0, 10, "ORG"], [272, 275, "ORG"], [156, 158, "GPE"], [163, 168, "GPE"], [64, 83, "DATE"], [218, 230, "DATE"], [37, 40, "ORG"], [5, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"], [68, 73, "NEW_ENTITY"], [41, 44, "CARDINAL"], [288, 295, "DATE"]]}],
["The PBoC on August 17 revamped its tool kit with a new benchmark interest rate.The loan prime rate, or LPR, has become the reference rate for banks pricing corporate loans and household mortgages.\n", {"entities": [[4, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"], [12, 21, "DATE"], [12, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [103, 106, "ORG"]]}],
["Foreign holding of Chinese bonds topped RMB2 trillion for the first time in July, according to data compiled by clearing houses China Central Depository and Clearing and Shanghai Clearing House.Foreign interest in Chinese bonds is partly driven by Bloomberg Barclays’s decision to begin adding Chinese government and policy bank bonds, as well as worries over prolonged trade discussions between the US and China\n", {"entities": [[128, 169, "ORG"], [62, 67, "ORDINAL"], [400, 402, "GPE"], [407, 412, "GPE"], [76, 80, "DATE"], [19, 26, "NORP"], [8, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"], [248, 268, "ORG"], [27, 32, "ASSET"], [294, 301, "NORP"], [214, 221, "NORP"], [170, 193, "ORG"]]}],
["Our passive equity funds benefit from our physical replication approach – where our portfolios are invested in the constituents of the underlying index, and do not use synthetic instruments, such as swaps and other derivatives, to mirror index performance.\n", {"entities": [[19, 24, "PRODUCT"], [63, 71, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our leading proprietary technology ensures the efficiency and accuracy of information – supporting consistent tracking and fund performance.Our proprietary technology has been designed by our investment teams to meet their rigorous and robust requirements to ensure cost savings and better performance outcomes for our funds and investors\n", {"entities": [[47, 57, "NEW_ENTITY"], [24, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Through considered implementation, we aim to find the optimal trade-off between temporary tracking error and transaction costs.The optimal balance and duration of implementation is important in achieving this objective and ultimately improves portfolio performance over time.\n", {"entities": [[35, 37, "NEW_ENTITY"], [19, 33, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Ongoing risk management includes investment operating parameters, tracking error risk, counterparty risk, exposure risk and the accuracy of analysis of performance attributions and exposures to different parts of the underlying market.\n", {"entities": [[13, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [54, 64, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["Index-based Investing -The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.  Where overseas investments are held the rate of currency exchange may also cause the value of such investments to fluctuate.\n", {"entities": [[27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["At the heart of our investment process is delivering close tracking error and managing tracking error budgets, while minimising the funds’ execution costs.We have a robust track record in providing competitively priced market access solutions.\n", {"entities": [[7, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [155, 157, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["UK based investors in HSBC ETFs plc are advised that they may not be afforded some of the protections conveyed by the Financial Services and Markets Act (2000),The Company is recognised in the United Kingdom by the Financial Conduct Authority under section 264 of the Act.\n", {"entities": [[211, 242, "ORG"], [114, 152, "ORG"], [0, 2, "GPE"], [189, 207, "GPE"], [257, 260, "CARDINAL"], [9, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [268, 271, "LAW"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [32, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["All applications are made on the basis of the current HSBC ETFs plc Prospectus, relevant Key Investor Information Document (“KIID”), Supplementary Information Document (SID) and Fund supplement, and most recent annual and semi-annual reports, which can be obtained upon request free of charge from HSBC Global Asset Management (UK) Limited, 8 Canada Square, Canary Wharf, London, E14 5HQ.UK, or from a stockbroker or financial adviser.\n", {"entities": [[33, 38, "NEW_ENTITY"], [372, 378, "GPE"], [4, 16, "NEW_ENTITY"], [298, 326, "ORG"], [358, 370, "GPE"], [380, 383, "GPE"], [133, 167, "LAW"], [54, 78, "ORG"], [343, 349, "GPE"], [125, 129, "ORG"], [341, 342, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["Shares purchased on the secondary market cannot usually be sold directly back to the Company.Investors must buy and sell shares on the secondary market with the assistance of an intermediary (e.g. a stockbroker) and may incur fees for doing so.In addition, investors may pay more than the current Net Asset Value per share when buying shares and may receive less than the current Net Asset Value per Share when selling them.\n", {"entities": [[0, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"], [34, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Risk management is central to our investment process before and after investment decisions are made.\n", {"entities": [[45, 52, "NEW_ENTITY"], [5, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["We offer equity market exposure to a range of global markets and carefully select indices where we can manage trading costs and liquidity.\n", {"entities": [[23, 31, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our tracking method and value-added approach to managing ETFs have enabled us to consistently produce returns that closely mirror the index within target tracking tolerances.\n", {"entities": [[13, 19, "NEW_ENTITY"], [57, 61, "ASSET"]]}],
["The shares in HSBC ETFs plc have not been and will not be offered for sale or sold in the United States of America, its territories or possessions and all areas subject to its jurisdiction, or to United States Persons.Affiliated companies of HSBC Global Asset Management (UK)Limited may make markets in HSBC ETFs plc.\n", {"entities": [[303, 316, "ORG"], [14, 27, "ORG"], [242, 270, "ORG"], [24, 27, "NEW_ENTITY"], [196, 217, "ORG"], [4, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"], [86, 114, "GPE"]]}],
["Exchange traded funds - HSBC Global Asset Management UK\n", {"entities": [[16, 21, "PRODUCT"], [0, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Investors and potential investors should read and note the risk warnings in the prospectus, relevant KIID and Fund supplement (where available) and additionally, in the case of retail clients, the information contained in the supporting SID.\n", {"entities": [[0, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [237, 240, "ORG"], [101, 105, "ORG"], [64, 72, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["When you look at ETFs, what do you see?\n", {"entities": [[17, 21, "ASSET"], [5, 8, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take a pragmatic approach to managing ETFs with two equally important objectives: close tracking and minimising costs.\n", {"entities": [[0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [51, 54, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["At HSBC we have traders located in key regional execution hubs.This is fundamental, as the expertise is connected to the market and exchange they operate in.This means our equity trades are handled by specialists with local knowledge, expertise and relationships, who are familiar with local service providers.At the end of the day, this can go a long way to deliver the best outcomes for investors.\n", {"entities": [[313, 331, "DATE"], [3, 7, "ORG"], [3, 7, "NEW_ENTITY"], [8, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The HSBC ETF range are sub-funds of HSBC ETFs plc (“the Company”), an investment company with variable capital and segregated liability between sub-funds, incorporated in Ireland as a public limited company, and is authorised by the Central Bank of Ireland.The company is constituted as an umbrella fund, with segregated liability between sub-funds.\n", {"entities": [[4, 12, "ORG"], [13, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [171, 178, "GPE"], [46, 49, "NEW_ENTITY"], [229, 256, "ORG"], [36, 49, "ORG"]]}],
["At HSBC we have implemented a screening of banned weapons such as cluster munitions, anti-personnel mines, chemical weapons etc.across the entire active and passive ranges – excluding investments in issuers that are involved in these weapons.\n", {"entities": [[3, 7, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 7, "ORG"], [8, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We have successfully managed index funds for clients since 1988, with dedicated portfolio management teams across global markets, leveraging our infrastructure and expertise.\n", {"entities": [[35, 40, "PRODUCT"], [59, 63, "DATE"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["In late 2009, we launched our first ETFs in Europe and currently have a suite of 29 funds which are built on our strong index tracking heritage, integrated platforms and disciplined processes.\n", {"entities": [[30, 35, "ORDINAL"], [14, 16, "NEW_ENTITY"], [8, 12, "NEW_ENTITY"], [44, 50, "LOC"], [81, 83, "CARDINAL"], [3, 12, "DATE"]]}],
["*To help continually improve our service and in the interest of security, we may record and/or monitor your communication with us.\n", {"entities": [[33, 40, "PRODUCT"], [74, 76, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Transparent end-to-end process focused on minimising implementation costs\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [19, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our index-based strategies cover global, regional and country indices using multiple vehicles such as ETFs, pooled funds, segregated mandates\n", {"entities": [[62, 69, "ASSET"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Index fund management has been at the heart of our business strategy since 1988; with this strong heritage we have developed our strategies to evolve with changing markets and client objectives.\n", {"entities": [[38, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [11, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [75, 79, "DATE"]]}],
["We minimise explicit and implicit transaction costs to mirror index returns as closely as possible\n", {"entities": [[46, 51, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Passive funds are only as good as the indices they track.Index selection is a major contributing factor to strong investment performance.\n", {"entities": [[8, 13, "PRODUCT"], [38, 45, "ASSET"]]}],
["We take a pragmatic approach to managing index funds with two equally important objectives: close tracking and increasing risk-adjusted returns\n", {"entities": [[58, 61, "CARDINAL"], [20, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["The large scale and the diversity of our index strategies allow us to deal at competitive prices and minimise costs for our clients\n", {"entities": [[10, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 57, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our tracking methodology and management approach focus on adding value; we aim for returns that closely track the index, while remaining within target tracking tolerances.\n", {"entities": [[65, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"], [40, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.Where overseas investments are held the rate of currency exchange may also cause the value of such investments to fluctuate.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Portfolios are implemented using physical replication and optimisation\n", {"entities": [[42, 53, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We select indices with the greatest transparency and liquidity that capture the best possible representation of the market\n", {"entities": [[10, 17, "ASSET"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our teams have a clear focus on managing risk at the start of the portfolio construction process and on a daily basis thereafter\n", {"entities": [[23, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [106, 111, "DATE"], [4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The Global Banking and Markets management team is led by Chief Executive and Group Managing Director Samir Assaf, reporting directly to HSBC Group Chief Executive, Noel Quinn.\n", {"entities": [[57, 72, "ORG"], [107, 112, "NEW_ENTITY"], [101, 112, "PERSON"], [164, 174, "PERSON"], [0, 30, "ORG"], [77, 82, "ORG"], [42, 46, "NEW_ENTITY"], [136, 162, "ORG"]]}],
["Whatever  the final objective – minimising the cost of capital, hedging, diversifying the  portfolio, or managing credit exposures – a robust investment and asset  allocation strategy could help  you    optimise returns while minimising risks.HSBC can support    you   by  supplementing your investment portfolio with structured products solutions ,  which can be used to access particular markets, isolate desired returns and  risks, protect against adverse market outcomes and take advantage of optimised  trading strategies.These  solutions can either be standardised  products or bespoke creations for individual clients.\n", {"entities": [[20, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 51, "NEW_ENTITY"], [243, 247, "ORG"]]}],
["In this increasingly interconnected world, ideas and capital are flowing around the globe, driving growth and disrupting the status quo.New trade routes emerge, propelling emerging economies to the spotlight and creating opportunities for companies and financial institutions worldwide.\n", {"entities": [[43, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 41, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Banking and Markets website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [25, 51, "ORG"], [52, 59, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 24, "ORG"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Benefit from a client coverage model that focuses on building deep long-term relationships with clients for advisory, financing and trading needs.\n", {"entities": [[31, 36, "NEW_ENTITY"], [37, 41, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We publish regularly updated information on our performance in relation to environmental, social and governance issues.Read more about our approach to ESG in the April 2019 report.\n", {"entities": [[162, 172, "DATE"], [151, 154, "ORG"], [29, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You could gain a competitive edge with customisable fund administration, global custody and sub-custody settlement, and corporate trust and loan agency services.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [29, 33, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our  product range covers all the main asset classes including Foreign Exchange  (FX), Equities, Fixed Income and Commodities.We also  develop  tailored solutions  in terms of wrappers, funding levels, minimum sizes and available currencies.\n", {"entities": [[45, 52, "NEW_ENTITY"], [63, 84, "ORG"], [13, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [97, 125, "ORG"]]}],
["Many of the industry's leading publications recognise our success as an emerging markets-led and financing-focused wholesale bank.\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [31, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Structured Products | Markets | Solutions | HSBC\n", {"entities": [[32, 41, "NEW_ENTITY"], [44, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["As the M&A advisor to many of the world’s multinational businesses, governments and institutions, HSBC is well positioned to deliver the financing and knowledge you need to meet your growth objectives.\n", {"entities": [[11, 18, "NEW_ENTITY"], [98, 102, "ORG"], [7, 10, "PERSON"], [98, 102, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You could manage trade risk, process trade transactions and fund trade activities more efficiently with HSBC’s full suite of trade and receivables finance products and services.\n", {"entities": [[71, 81, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [104, 108, "ORG"]]}],
["Our  extensive range of products is combined with knowledgeable support, competitive  pricing and  dedicated after-sales  service.This is backed by the breadth and depth of our global network that  gives you access to international markets, and enables us to support clients  around the world in various sectors including institutional investors, hedge  funds, retail product distributors, governments, supranationals, and  corporates.\n", {"entities": [[15, 20, "NEW_ENTITY"], [24, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"], [403, 417, "PERSON"]]}],
["global team of structuring and sales professionals offers in-depth expertise in  analysing, structuring and pricing these products.\n", {"entities": [[7, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"], [15, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["You could capitalise on growth opportunities by leveraging the global expertise and in-depth knowledge of our experienced capital financing solutions specialists.\n", {"entities": [[31, 44, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our comprehensive range of product and solutions could be combined and customised to meet your business’ specific growth ambitions and financial objectives.\n", {"entities": [[18, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"], [27, 34, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["The portfolios are monitored daily and rebalanced periodically to ensure that they remain in line with their agreed risk budgets\n", {"entities": [[93, 97, "NEW_ENTITY"], [29, 34, "DATE"], [4, 14, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["HSBC Global Strategy Portfolios primarily use passive investment products, to deliver cost-efficiency, namely index tracking funds and ETFs, to implement portfolio asset allocation\n", {"entities": [[21, 31, "NEW_ENTITY"], [65, 73, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 4, "ORG"]]}],
["The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not receive back the amount originally invested.Where overseas investments are held the rate of currency exchange may also affect the value of investments.The global nature of the funds means that part of the fund portfolios could be invested within emerging market regions.These investments are by their nature higher risk and potentially more volatile than those inherent in established markets.\n", {"entities": [[4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["View our latest webinar:what's next?\n", {"entities": [[24, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 23, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Investors and potential investors should read the relevant key investor information document and full prospectus for full details of the risks involved before making an investment decision.The HSBC Global Strategy Fund Portfolios are sub-funds of HSBC Open Funds, an Open Ended Investment Company that is authorised in the UK by the Financial Conduct Authority.The Authorised Corporate Director and Investment Manager is HSBC Global Asset Management (UK)Limited.\n", {"entities": [[189, 229, "ORG"], [247, 262, "ORG"], [0, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [267, 296, "ORG"], [421, 449, "ORG"], [84, 92, "NEW_ENTITY"], [329, 360, "ORG"], [323, 325, "GPE"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["A suite of five risk-targeted portfolios to match your clients profile with a highly cost-efficient access to global markets\n", {"entities": [[2, 7, "NEW_ENTITY"], [11, 15, "CARDINAL"], [30, 40, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["*Copyright © 2019 - Morningstar UK Limited.All Rights Reserved.Ratings should not be taken as a recommendation.The HSBC Global Strategy Balanced Portfolio – Retail X Acc – and HSBC Global Strategy Dynamic Portfolio – Retail X Acc – are both rated 5 Stars as at 30 September 2019.\n", {"entities": [[247, 248, "CARDINAL"], [47, 53, "NEW_ENTITY"], [43, 62, "WORK_OF_ART"], [176, 229, "ORG"], [261, 278, "DATE"], [96, 110, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 42, "ORG"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Cost-efficient deliveryso investors benefit from low overall investment costs\n", {"entities": [[72, 77, "NEW_ENTITY"], [26, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["FE Alpha Manager ratings do not constitute investment advice offered by FE and should not be used as the sole basis for making any investment decision.All rights reserved.\n", {"entities": [[72, 74, "ORG"], [17, 24, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 8, "ORG"], [54, 60, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["Index-based Investing -The value of investments and any income from them can go down as well as up and investors may not get back the amount originally invested.  Where overseas investments are held the rate of currency exchange may also cause the value of such investments to fluctuate.\n", {"entities": [[27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We minimise explicit and implicit transaction costs to mirror index returns as closely as possible\n", {"entities": [[46, 51, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Passive funds are only as good as the indices they track.Index selection is a major contributing factor to strong investment performance.\n", {"entities": [[8, 13, "PRODUCT"], [38, 45, "ASSET"]]}],
["We take a pragmatic approach to managing index funds with two equally important objectives: close tracking and increasing risk-adjusted returns\n", {"entities": [[58, 61, "CARDINAL"], [20, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Please be aware that the external site policies will differ from our website terms and conditions and privacy policy.The next site will open in a new browser window or tab.\n", {"entities": [[77, 82, "NEW_ENTITY"], [39, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We take your security very seriously.In order to protect you and our systems, we are making changes to all HSBC websites that means some of the oldest web browser versions will no longer be able to access these sites.Generally, the latest versions of a browser (like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, etc.) and an operating system family (like Microsoft Windows, MacOS) have the most up-to-date security features.\n", {"entities": [[301, 313, "ORG"], [377, 382, "ORG"], [286, 299, "ORG"], [358, 367, "ORG"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"], [13, 21, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 111, "ORG"], [267, 284, "ORG"]]}],
["The large scale and the diversity of our index strategies allow us to deal at competitive prices and minimise costs for our clients\n", {"entities": [[10, 15, "NEW_ENTITY"], [47, 57, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our index-based strategies cover global, regional and country indices\n", {"entities": [[62, 69, "ASSET"], [16, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our tracking methodology and management approach focus on adding value; we aim for returns that closely track the index, while remaining within target tracking tolerances.\n", {"entities": [[65, 70, "NEW_ENTITY"], [40, 48, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Our teams have a clear focus on managing risk - at the start of the portfolio construction process and on a daily basis thereafter\n", {"entities": [[23, 28, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [108, 113, "DATE"]]}],
["HSBC was one of the first providers of index trackers in the UK.Since 1988, when we launched the first fund, we have expanded our product range in line with the changing needs of clients around the world.\n", {"entities": [[0, 4, "NEW_ENTITY"], [26, 35, "NEW_ENTITY"], [97, 102, "ORDINAL"], [0, 4, "ORG"], [57, 74, "DATE"], [9, 12, "CARDINAL"], [20, 25, "ORDINAL"]]}],
["You are leaving the HSBC Global Asset Management website.\n", {"entities": [[0, 3, "NEW_ENTITY"], [16, 48, "ORG"], [49, 56, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["I have read and accept the terms and wish to continue into this site.I confirm that I am a Financial Intermediary based in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[0, 1, "NEW_ENTITY"], [127, 129, "GPE"], [84, 113, "ORG"], [27, 32, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["In 1988, HSBC was one of the first providers of index trackers in the UK.\n", {"entities": [[18, 21, "CARDINAL"], [3, 7, "NEW_ENTITY"], [70, 72, "GPE"], [9, 13, "ORG"], [29, 34, "ORDINAL"], [9, 13, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 7, "DATE"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"Terms and Conditions\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 81, "WORK_OF_ART"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Portfolios are implemented using physical replication and optimisation\n", {"entities": [[42, 53, "NEW_ENTITY"], [0, 10, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Beginning of dialog window.It begins with a heading called \"You are leaving the HSBC AMG website.\".Escape will cancel and close the window.\n", {"entities": [[99, 105, "ORG"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [85, 88, "ORG"], [27, 29, "NEW_ENTITY"], [20, 26, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["We select indices with the greatest transparency and liquidity and that capture the best possible representation of the market\n", {"entities": [[10, 17, "ASSET"], [0, 2, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["Experienced passive manager –our experience and knowledge has allowed us to develop a robust tracking methodology and management approach, focused on adding value for investors\n", {"entities": [[33, 43, "NEW_ENTITY"], [129, 137, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The investment process for passive fixed income consists of 5 steps which include; benchmark review, determine investable universe, portfolio modelling and construction, ongoing portfolio management and portfolio implementation.With our dual objective reflected in each step of our process.\n", {"entities": [[41, 47, "NEW_ENTITY"], [15, 22, "NEW_ENTITY"], [60, 61, "CARDINAL"]]}],
["This Site is intended for Financial Intermediaries in the UK only.\n", {"entities": [[5, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"], [36, 50, "NEW_ENTITY"], [58, 60, "GPE"], [26, 50, "ORG"]]}],
["Our process is underpinned by our extensive proprietary resources and tools which have been developed over the last two decades, allowing us to align our passive and active fixed income platforms globally.\n", {"entities": [[56, 65, "NEW_ENTITY"], [107, 127, "DATE"], [4, 11, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["If you are seeing this message, we have detected that you are using an older, unsupported browser.\n", {"entities": [[23, 30, "NEW_ENTITY"], [3, 6, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
["The level of yields is not guaranteed and may rise or fall in the future\n", {"entities": [[13, 19, "NEW_ENTITY"], [4, 9, "NEW_ENTITY"]]}],
